clocklink.com 2014-06-25

# Seattle Domain, Web & Email Hosting : Privacy Policy

## PSPINC takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

### What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how PSPINC treats personal information that PSPINC collects and receives, including information related to your past use of PSPINC products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

### General

PSPINC collects personal information when you register with PSPINC, when you use PSPINC products or services, when you visit PSPINC pages or the pages of certain PSPINC partners. PSPINC may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with PSPINC and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

PSPINC collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.

PSPINC automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, PSPINC cookie information, and the page you request.

PSPINC uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

PSPINC does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with PSPINC under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help PSPINC communicate with you about offers from PSPINC and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of PSPINC's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if PSPINC is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, PSPINC will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

PSPINC does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

### Cookies

PSPINC may set and access PSPINC cookies on your computer.

### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

PSPINC may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your PSPINC account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at:

PSPINC  
Pacific Software Publishing, Inc.  
1404 140th Place NE,  
Bellevue, WA 98007 USA  
(425) 957-0808

This policy was created on August 16, 2004
